vapor4life.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy | Electronic Cigarette | E-Cigs by Vapor4Life

**Your consent**  
By using our website, you consent to our privacy policy and our terms and conditions, as explained below. This policy was last modified on June 6, 2012 and governs the use of our website and information associated with the purchase of products through our website. We encourage you to refer to this policy periodically so that you understand our current privacy policies.

**What information do we collect?**

  * We collect information from you when you register on the website, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another website feature.
  * When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our website anonymously.
  * We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.
  * Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use cookies?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

**How do we use your information?**  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other website features in the following ways:

  * To personalize your website experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other website feature.
  * For marketing and promotional purposes.
  * If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other website features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.
  * We may combine information about you that we collect online, over the telephone, and from any third-party sources.

**How do we protect visitor information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We do not store any credit card information.

**Do we use cookies?**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the website's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use two types of cookies—session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies exist only for the duration of time you have your internet browser open when you visit our site and are used for functions such as remembering and processing items in your shopping cart. Persistent cookies do not disappear when you exit your browser, but instead persist each time you visit our website. These cookies are used to help us better understand your preferences based on previous or current website activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about website traffic and website interaction so that we can offer better website experiences and tools in the future.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our website visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Mozilla Firefox or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your website experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting Customer Service.

**Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?**  
Except as described below, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. The term "outside parties" does not include Vapor4Life. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our website policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?**  
To modify your e-mail subscriptions or other information that you have provided to us, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to e-mail production schedules you may receive emails already in production.

To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our website and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may continue to maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for internal record keeping purposes.

**Third party links**  
In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our website. These linked websites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked websites. These linked websites are only for your convenience and therefore you access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, Vapor4Life seeks to protect the integrity of our website and welcomes any feedback about these linked websites (including if a specific link does not work).

**Changes to our policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this “Vapor4Life Privacy Policy” page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

**California Privacy Rights**  
California Civil Code §§ 1798.83-.84 provide users that are California residents with a right to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we may share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As noted above, we do not currently provide personally identifiable information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. However, if you are a California resident and would like to receive a separate written notice to this effect, please submit a written request to Vapor4Life, Inc., 4100 Commercial Avenue, Northbrook, IL 60062. In your request, please specify that you want a copy of your “California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow 30 days for us to respond.

**Questions and feedback**  
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy or this policy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue by contacting us via phone at (847) 944-8200 or by mail at Vapor 4 Life, Inc., 4100 Commercial Avenue, Northbrook, IL 60062.

**Online Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**  
Please visit our Terms and Conditions section, which establishes use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
